https://www.snarkland.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
WhatWhat
Select Category
Adventures in Dog Walking  (23)
birthdays  (23)
Consumables  (41)
Fiction  (4)
Gainesville  (110)
Genealogy  (4)
HaldeCraft  (1,033)
Ceramics  (271)
Animals  (25)
Decorative  (54)
Figurines  (35)
Functional  (101)
Kitchen  (45)
Planters  (24)
Craft room organization  (12)
Craft Shows  (31)
Custom Orders  (6)
Etsy  (19)
friends shops  (7)
Etsy treasuries featuring HaldeCraft  (67)
Events  (7)
Free Advice  (7)
Gift guides  (2)
HaldeBalm  (12)
HaldeCraft ceramics  (73)
HaldeCrate  (19)
HaldeKnits  (11)
HaldeSpun  (8)
Sale  (59)
Shop Updates  (110)
Soap  (44)
Studio Move  (9)
This Week in HaldeCraft  (236)
Yarn  (100)
Home and Garden  (90)
Knitting  (286)
For the feet  (102)
For the hands  (18)
For the head  (34)
For the home  (32)
For the neck  (13)
For the shoulders  (6)
For the torso  (18)
HaldeKnit patterns  (2)
Yearly recap  (6)
Links  (85)
Happy Things  (12)
linkdump  (72)
Monday Musings  (30)
Movies  (9)
music  (122)
My Random Life  (545)
Navel Gazing  (57)
Obituaries  (11)
Patreon  (2)
Pets  (79)
Photograpy  (161)
Friday Photo  (92)
My Family Was (and still is) Awesome  (23)
Tiltshift  (25)
Poll of the Week  (60)
Other random polls  (5)
Question of the Week  (69)
Childhood  (8)
Family and Friends  (11)
Food and Drink  (3)
Fun and Sport  (1)
Habits  (9)
Hobbies and Fun  (4)
Holidays  (1)
Movies and TV  (1)
Outlook  (14)
Politics  (5)
Spirituality  (6)
Work  (5)
Ramblings  (56)
Randomosity  (28)
Rants  (49)
Sewing  (10)
Snarkland  (19)
Souvenirs  (49)
Spinning  (41)
Off the Wheel 2006  (1)
Off the Wheel 2007  (1)
Off the Wheel 2008  (1)
Off the Wheel 2009  (8)
Off the Wheel 2010  (18)
Off the Wheel 2011  (2)
Off the Wheel 2013  (5)
Tutorial  (2)
TV  (19)
Uncategorized  (130)
Weaving  (14)
for the neck  (9)
Wheresearch me
Search for:
Search
A Day in the (Work)Life
haldecraft
Maker of thrown, hand-built, and slipcast ceramics; dyer and spinner of yarn; writer of science fiction; watcher of people and nature.
I thought these had sold out, but there was one st
Load More...
Follow on Instagram
Home Privacy Policy
Who we are
Our website address is: http://www.snarkland.com.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Who we share your data with
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
Lorena Haldeman
haldechick@gmail.com
Patreon features in this website
In order to enable you to use this website with Patreon services, we save certain functionally important Patreon information about you in this website if you log in with Patreon.
These include your Patreon user id, Patreon username, your first, last names and your vanity name. Additionally, the id of your campaign at Patreon and your campaign’s Patreon URL are also saved.
If you request that your data be deleted from this website, this data will also be deleted and Patreon functionality will not work. You would need to register on this website and log in to this website with Patreon again in order to re-populate this data and have Patreon functionality working again.
Related Posts:FlickSmugAgramFive of my Pinterest boards that I’m enjoyingI’ll be back soon!17 ways you’re running your business wrong (#3…Works-in-progress Wednesday (08/12/15)How much email do you get from HaldeCraft?The January #planwithmechallenge (days 6-15)Pinterest! I love you, I hate you.
Back to Top
